hi ladies and gentlemen uh this video is
going to be in response to a blog post I
posted a couple days ago uh it was
titled um please vote should I avoid
embedding pictures showing great glute
development in my blog and uh I was
really proud of myself because I figured
out how to how to uh pull um create a
poll on my blog all all by myself and
I'm not very techsavvy so uh thought I
was pretty nifty there but uh uh I
really just wanted to hear different
people's opinions on this because I've
gotten mixed signals uh over the past
few years on my blog some people saying
I love your pictures some people saying
I don't like them uh and so this was a
great opportunity to not only um acquire
some statistics but also to hear um you
know feedback so I not only got um
quantitative data I also got qualitative
data um which was nice because I learned
a lot through through both uh forms of
data
so
uh uh for the survey I will show you the
results um so I'll show you the camera
screen
um
so
um here are the results so the first
question as you can see I got around I
don't know around
2,200 people voted so the first question
uh was do you find the the pictures I
embed into my blog to be offensive or
distasteful as you can see 92% of people
do not find them offensive and 8% of
people do find them to be offensive so
this what here's what's crazy when there
was 100 votes this was the same
percentage and it never deviated the
whole way through it it never deviated
more than one percentage Point um it was
always 92 and8 the whole time through
crazy so pretty confident that 8% of
people are offended and 92% are not next
question do you find the pictures I
embedded in my blog to be motivating or
inspirational and this never changed as
well this was well actually it was it
was 85% most of the way through 85 and
15 and then towards the end it became 86
and 14% so 86% of people find the
pictures inspirational and motivating do
you want me to avoid embedding photos
that depict great glute development um
93% of people do not want me to stop
seven people 7% of people do and then
what is your gender was the last
question this was the only one that
changed uh the first day it was actually
52% female and 48% male and then then uh
after a couple of days that flip-flo so
it ended up being 53% male and 47%
female which was surprising cuz I
actually had no clue uh how many people
um how many like what what was a
breakdown of people who read my blog and
so now I know it's a pretty even split
which was nice because
um I didn't know at you know it's good
to know those things so what's cool
about this blog is that uh it is about
glutes and women love glutes but men
love strength training so I think for
that reason I have an equal blend of
male and female readership um so now I
showed you the data uh the quantitative
data the survey results and now I want
to talk about the comments the
qualitative data that I got back so um
it's
it's very telling some of the responses
and I read every single person's
response
and I I take that stuff very seriously
I'm I'm here to learn from you guys
that's the whole point of it this was
not to try to justify my ways or
anything like that so first to tell you
I you know I I'm a fan of butts
obviously I love posting these pictures
I love my picture collection if you guys
could see the folder of glute pictures
that I have on my computer it's insane
I've got hundreds so whenever I I'm
always researching on glutes and so
whenever I see a nice picture I'll save
it I've also been on some Facebook pages
and things that have like hundreds of
pictures so I'll save
them and you know as you can see from
the comments some people love them and
feel the same way I do and some people
don't so
um there were 215 comments on the blog
and this is as of it's 11:30 right now
on uh on Monday night so as of Monday
Night 11:30 Arizona time there have been
comments only two people basically in
the comments said you should stop I
don't like I don't like the pictures and
63 PE of the 215 responses were
basically keep it up I love the pictures
they're motivating something like that
so um but here's where I learned the
most um and you think this would be
common sense but it it's not so common
sense to me so what's nice is um I got
some specific feedback so about 39
different people in the comment section
said that they don't like the lingerie
pictures the hypersexual pictures you
know the
pictures where the woman has her back
extremely arched into you know massive
anter pelvic tilt lumbar
hyperextension
um and
31 people said said they want more
pictures of
men
um 23 people said they want more real
world pictures and more
variety uh nine people basically said I
have crappy questions um Laura a
commenter named Laura gave gave me much
better questions that I could have asked
in the poll and uh as did opilia they
both offered some really good feedback
there um in retrospect I probably should
have posed better questions but bear in
mind this was my first poll I wanted to
keep it simple um five people said they
wanted before and after
pictures uh 16 people said basically
that they like my they like the blog
they like the pictures but they're
really not safe for work or not safe for
home and that you know they have kids or
they wouldn't want their co-workers
seeing them or they'd be embarrassed or
maybe their spouse house um which I
totally
understand uh two people said that I
should have something in my blog where I
offer a code where you can choose
whether you want the pictures or not I
don't know how to do that maybe my web
guy does but uh I don't think that's
necessary one person said they want more
male flutes and um I'm pretty sure that
was a typo for glutes but in case it's
the other thing I don't think I want to
go there uh one person uh es
estefania said uh mentioned that she
doesn't want the banana coconut flower
hypersexualization and that had to be
the com that that that one takes the
cake that's the best comment and that
was just um an error with her her phone
basically um typed out a recipe when she
hit
autocorrect and then one lady Molly
compared me to Thomas Jefferson and said
don't be Thomas Jefferson and and I
still don't understand that because I
thought Thomas Jefferson was a good guy
and uh you was like one of the
forefathers of of our country and so I
don't I still don't understand that so
anyway those were the the 215
comments and now uh basically let me
just ramble for a bit so um I think the
passionate people speak out more in the
comment section we really need to see
both see each other's points of view so
I'm more towards the hey this is artwork
and you know it's glutes aren't you know
it's just a muscle it's sexy it's
inspiring I'm towards this end and I
need to see how people feel towards this
end and the people towards this end need
to see need to see how the people
towards this end feel so um we need to
meet in the middle we need to see each
other's uh viewpoints see both sides so
um I'm I've learned I've I've learned a
lot through reading the comments and uh
and what I want to say is I would if I
did stop posting pictures Al together I
would be doing a disservice to the
majority there were a lot of people said
these pictures inspire me so I would be
um you know doing harm uh I would be
missing those people if I stopped
posting pictures completely ever as
pointed out in the comment section by a
lot of different ladies said Brett
you're missing the point here it's not
you don't need to stop posting pictures
it's the type of pictures so what's cool
is I don't feel like this is much of a
compromise here um basically people want
more men more male pictures more before
and after pictures more gym shots and
less [__] stuff so those four things
the less [__] stuff that's easy uh the
more gym shots now now I I will tell you
when I'm training people you know I'm
supposed to be coaching them and I I I'm
on Instagram now I try to capture
pictures but sometimes it's hard because
I'm like coaching them and I'm trying to
take video clips or pictures and um you
know it's I feel like a sometimes like
I'm a crappy trainer or coach because
I'm more concerned with getting the
picture than I am coaching them and
making sure they have good form and
spotting them but uh I work out at a gym
now most of them are doing hip thrust
they're all you know a lot of
powerlifters they do their squats their
deadlifts uh and so I can get good
pictures there um a lot of them have
very good glut so I can get more
pictures uh in that in that respect I
can also reach out to um you know people
colleagues in the industry and tell them
to take some good glute pictures so I
can try and do that uh as for the before
and after pictures I think I've posted
more than anyone in this industry as far
as before and after pictures I post my
own clients
as well as um you know people who send
me pictures so all I can ask for is keep
sending me in before and after pictures
if you have good before and after
pictures you want to show off send me
them and I'll post them
um um but I try and do that on my random
blog posts and I've been doing that the
last couple months and uh I'll keep
doing it as long as I keep getting
people sending me pictures and as for
the mail pictures uh I will tell you if
you type in like on Google Images nice
butts or great glutes or something like
that you get mostly pictures of women
there aren't as many pictures of men and
so uh to get you know you think you
would type in like male glutes and there
would be all these awesome male butts
but I am pretty picky about male glutes
Sometimes women might think they're nice
male glutes but I can tell they just
have decent shape but they don't even
work out they don't they didn't earn
those glutes through you know lifting
weights or playing sports and I don't
sometimes they're just like they might
be round but they're flabby or something
so I have I have um high expectations
for male glutes I want them to be
muscular and have that athletic look and
there aren't that many pictures of like
an athlete you know in spandex or
something showing off his glutes but
there are tons of pictures of
powerlifters and Olympic lifters and you
know athletes and things like that but
you know if you want to show off their
glutes they need to be more in like
spandex or underwear but I will try to
find more of those and uh embed embed
those into the
blog anyway uh it's going on 12 and a
half minutes I'm going to wrap it up
here but thank you very much this was a
very uh educational and informative
experience for me I appreciate your
input and uh I will make changes based
on your input this is not much of a
compromise and so I'm going to keep
posting pictures but just not as much uh
[__] uh you know lerie hypersex ual
stuff um and I think I'll please
everyone so again thank you very much uh
I'm going to do more polls in the future
so I hope you will continue to give me
input so I can better please my
readership thanks for watching